<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>Ideology Development+</name>
	<author>Garwel</author>
	<url>https://github.com/GarwelGarwel/IdeologyDevelopmentPlus</url>
	<packageId>Garwel.IdeologyDevelopmentPlus</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>Ideology Development+ overhauls reforming of fluid ideoligions.
	
A reform now requires varying amount of development points, determined by what you change. The cost consists of the following parts:

- Base reform cost, which is based on the number of followers of this ideoligion, number of like-minded factions and the number of previous reforms. The formula is configurable.

- Cost of added and removed memes, scaled with their impact. Structure and style memes are free.

- Cost of changed precepts. The more beneficial precept you choose, the higher the cost. You may also go for a worse precept and get back a point or two.

- For spectrum precepts, jumping several steps at a time costs more than gradual changes.

Notes:

- You can now make any ideoligion fluid. Yes, even those of other factions! Of course, to actually change them, you'll need to get some development points. The game will also offer you to make your player ideoligion fluid, if you forgot to do it.

- Acquisition of development points is doubled (by default). So when the game says you will receive 2 dev points for a ritual, you will actually get 4, and so on.

- Dev point cap is removed (i.e. you can accumulate as many dev points as you want).

- In Surprise Precepts Mode (enable in mod settings), you only choose memes (and also culture) and precepts are randomly auto-generated. You can't preview or change them, but they are free.

- Most values can be tweaked to your liking.

Obviously, Ideology DLC is required. So is Harmony.

Should be compatible with most mods except those that also change the ideo development. May need additional patches for better balancing custom precepts. Patches for ideoligions from Biotech and Vanilla Vehicles Expanded are included.

Github: https://github.com/GarwelGarwel/IdeologyDevelopmentPlus</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</packageId>
			<displayName>Ideology</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
