<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>Ideology Development+</name>
	<author>Garwel</author>
	<url>https://github.com/GarwelGarwel/IdeologyDevelopmentPlus</url>
	<packageId>Garwel.IdeologyDevelopmentPlus</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>Ideology Development+ overhauls reforming of fluid ideoligions.
	
A reform now requires varying amount of development points, determined by what you change. The cost consists of the following parts:

- Base reform cost, which increases with every reform until it reaches a ceiling. By default, it goes from 10 to 20 dev points.

- Cost of added and removed memes, scaled with their impact (2 to 6 points). Structure and style are free.

- Changing precepts costs normally 1 point per precept, but it increases for spectrum-like precepts (such as number of spouses) when you want to jump several steps at a time (e.g. from having 1 spouse to having 4).

- Adding or removing certain precepts that have a serious gameplay impact may cost or reimburse dev points. E.g. adopting Very Fast Research will cost you 4 more points; adopting Very Slow Research will give you 4 dev points.

Notes:

- Acquisition of development points is doubled (by default). So when the game says you will receive 2 dev points for a ritual, you will actually get 4, and so on.

- Dev point cap is removed (i.e. you can accumulate as many dev points as you want)

- In Surprise Precepts Mode (enable in mod settings), you only choose memes (and also culture) and precepts are randomly auto-generated. You can't preview or change them, but they are free

- Can be added to an ongoing game, even if your ideoligion is not fluid (you will be offered to make it such). Removing it mid-game will cause a one-time harmless error message

- Most values can be tweaked to your liking

Obviously, Ideology DLC is required. So is Harmony.

Should be compatible with most mods except those that also change the ideo development. May need additional patches for better balancing custom precepts.

Let me know if you think the balance is off somewhere.

Github: https://github.com/GarwelGarwel/IdeologyDevelopmentPlus</description>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</packageId>
			<displayName>Ideology</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
